blackshotonline.com 2016-06-28

# PlayOne.Asia

### INTRODUCTION

PLAYONE ASIA SDN BHD respects the privacy of individuals with regard to personal data and is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and strives to provide a safe, secure user experience. This privacy policy is formulated in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 ("Act"), which describes how your information is collected and used and your choices with respect to your Personal Data. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

By using the services, registering for an account with us, visiting our website, or accessing the services, you acknowledge and agree that you accept the practices, requirements, and/or policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent to us collecting, using, disclosing and/or processing your personal data as described herein. IF YOU DO NOT CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES OR ACCESS OUR WEBSITE. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes or the amended Privacy Policy on our website. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

### DEFINITIONS

(i) “Playone Asia”, “Us”, “our” and/or “we” means PLAYONE ASIA SDN BHD(PLAYONE ASIA) and its affiliates and related corporations and shall include our agents, employees, contractors; 

(ii) “Personal data” data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified from that data, or from that data and other information to which an organization has or is likely to have access. Common examples of personal data could include name, identification number and contact information. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTED BY PLAYONE ASIA

The personal data that Playone Asia may collect includes but is not limited to: name, email address, date of birth, billing address, bank account and payment information, telephone number, gender, any other information about the user when the user signs up to use our services or website, and when the user uses the services or website, as well as information related to how the user uses our services or website, aggregate data on content the user engages with. If you do not want us to collect the aforementioned information/personal data, you may opt out at any time by notifying in writing about it. 

### PURPOSE OF COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

(i) to register and/or use our services or site, or open an account with us; 

(ii) to submit any form, including, but not limited to, application forms or other forms relating to any of our products and services, whether online or by way of a physical form; 

(iii) toenter into any agreement or provide other documentation or information in respect of your interactions with us, or when you use our products and services; 

(iv) tointeract with us, such as via telephone calls (which may be recorded), letters, fax, face-to-face meetings, social media platforms and emails; 

(v) touse our electronic services, or interact with us via our website or use services on our website. This includes, without limitation, through cookies which we may deploy when you interact with our applications or website; 

(vi) tocarry out transactions through our website or services; 

(vii) to provide us with feedback or complaints;   
(viii) toregister for a contest, for games or game specific events; 

(ix) during your gameplay; 

(x) tosubmit your personal data to us for any reason. 

### COOKIES

We may from time to time implement "cookies" or other features to allow us or third parties to collect or share information that will help us improve our site and the services we offer, or help us offer new services and features. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your computer or device and tell us how and when the services or website are used or visited, by how many people and to track movements within our website. We may link cookie information to personal data. Cookies also link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart, for example. Cookies are also used to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of our site or the services. 

### VIEWING AND DOWNLOADING CONTENT AND ADVERTISING

As with browsing web pages, when you watch content and advertising or download games and access other software on our site or through the services, most of the same information is sent to us (including, without limitation, IP Address, operating system, etc.); but, instead of page views, your computer sends us information on the content, advertisement or game viewed and/or software installed by the services and the website and time. Additionally, the services allow us to collect information regarding the games you have installed and uninstalled on your computer and what time you start and stop playing a game. 

### COMMUNITY & SUPPORT

We provide customer service support through email and feedback forms. In order to provide customer support, we will ask for your email address. Aside from this information, we do not ask for any personal data to provide customer support. We only use information received from customer support requests, including, without limitation, email addresses, for customer support services and we do not transfer to or share this information with any third parties. 

You can also post questions and answer other user questions in our community forums. Our forum and messaging services allow you to participate in our community; to do so, we maintain information, such as your User ID, contact list and status messages, including what game you are currently playing (if you explicitly choose to enable this option). In addition, these and similar services in the future may require us to maintain your User ID and password. 

### SETTING UP AN ACCOUNT

In order to use certain functionalities of the services, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal data. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us with your name and email address as well as a user name that you select. We also ask for certain information about yourself such as your age, birth/date/telephone number, email address, shipping address, photo identification, bank account details, age, date of birth, gender and interests. Upon activating an account, you will select a user name and password. Your user name and password will be used so you can securely access and maintain your account. 

### USAGE OF INFORMATION

We may collect, use, disclose and/or process your personal data for one or more of the following purposes: (i) to consider and/or process your application/transaction with us or your transactions or communications with third parties via the services; 

(ii) to manage, operate, provide and/or administer your use of and/or access to our services and our website, as well as your relationship and user account with us; 

(iii) to manage, operate, administer and provide you with as well as to facilitate the provision of our services, including, without limitation, remembering your preferences; 

(iv) to tailor your experience through the services by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to access your account and submit information to us and allowing us to contact you, if necessary; 

(v) to respond to, process, deal with or complete a transaction and/or to fulfil your requests for certain products and services and notify you of service issues and unusual account actions; 

(vi) to enforce our Terms of service or any applicable end user license agreements; 

(vii) to protect personal safety and the rights, property or safety of others; 

(viii) for identification and/or verification; 

(ix) to maintain and administer any software updates and/or other updates and support that may be required from time to time to ensure the smooth running of our services; 

(x) to deal with or facilitate customer service, carry out your instructions, deal with or respond to any enquiries given by (or purported to be given by) you or on your behalf; 

(xi) to contact you or communicate with you via voice call, text message and/or fax message, email and/or postal mail or otherwise for the purposes of administering and/or managing your relationship with us or your use of our services, such as but not limited to communicating administrative information to you relating to our services. You acknowledge and agree that such communication by us could be by way of the mailing of correspondence, documents or notices to you, which could involve disclosure of certain personal data about you to bring about delivery of the same as well as on the external cover of envelopes/mail packages; 

(xii) to inform you when another user has sent you a private message or posted a comment for you on the site; 

(xiii) to conduct research, analysis and development activities (including, but not limited to, data analytics, surveys, product and service development and/or profiling), to analyze how you use our services, to improve our services or products and/or to enhance your customer experience; 

(xiv) to allow for advertising and other audits and surveys to, among other things, validate the size and composition of our target audience, and understand their experience with Playone Asia ’s services; 

(xv) where you give us your prior consent, for marketing and in this regard, to send you by various modes of communication such as postal mail, email, location-based services or otherwise, marketing and promotional information and materials relating to products and/or services (including, without limitation, products and/or services of third parties whom Playone Asia may collaborate or tie up with) that Playone Asia (and/or its affiliates or related corporations) may be selling, marketing or promoting, whether such products or services exist now or are created in the future 

(xvi) to respond to legal processes or to comply with or as required by any applicable law, governmental or regulatory requirements of any relevant jurisdiction, including, without limitation, meeting the requirements to make disclosure under the requirements of any law binding on Playone Asia or on its related corporations or affiliates; 

(xvii) to produce statistics and research for internal and statutory reporting and/or record-keeping requirements; 

(xviii) to carry out due diligence or other screening activities (including, without limitation, background checks) in accordance with legal or regulatory obligations or our risk management procedures that may be required by law or that may have been put in place by us; 

(xix) to audit our services or Playone Asia 's business; 

(xx) to prevent or investigate any fraud, unlawful activity, omission or misconduct, whether relating to your use of our services or any other matter arising from your relationship with us, and whether or not there is any suspicion of the aforementioned; 

(xxi) to store, host, back up (whether for disaster recovery or otherwise) of your personal data, whether within or outside of your jurisdiction; 

(xxii) to deal with and/or facilitate a business asset transaction or a potential business asset transaction, where such transaction involves Playone Asia as a participant or involves only a related corporation or affiliate of Playone Asia as a participant or involves Playone Asia and/or any one or more of Playone Asia's related corporations or affiliates as participant(s), and there may be other third party organizations who are participants in such transaction. A “business asset transaction” refers to the purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other acquisition, disposal or financing of an organization or a portion of an organization or of any of the business or assets of an organization; and/or 

(xxiii) any other purposes which we notify you of at the time of obtaining your consent. 

This may require, among other things, disclosing your gaming history and/or disclosing records showing which games were viewed by which IP addresses. We will also share statistical and demographic information about our users and their use of the services with suppliers of advertisements and programming. This would not include anything that could be used to identify you specifically or to discover individual information about you. 

Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access personal data transmitted to or contained on the site, technologies may malfunction or not work as anticipated, or someone might access, abuse or misuse information through no fault of ours. We will nevertheless deploy reasonable security arrangements to protect your personal data as required by the Privacy Laws; however there can inevitably be no guarantee of absolute security such as but not limited to when unauthorized disclosure arises from malicious and sophisticated hacking by malcontents through no fault of ours. 

Our services enable users to share personal information with each other, in almost all occasions without Playone Asia’s involvement, to complete transactions. In a typical transaction, users may have access to each other’s name, User ID, email address and other contact and postage information. Our Terms of service require that users in possession of another user’s personal data (the “Receiving Party”) must (i) comply with all applicable Privacy Laws; (ii) allow the other user (the “Disclosing Party”) to remove him/herself from the Receiving Party’s database; and (iii) allow the Disclosing Party to review what information have been collected about them by the Receiving Party. 

### CHILDREN

The services are not intended for children under the age of 10. We do not knowingly collect or maintain any personal data or non-personally-identifiable information from anyone under the age of 10 nor is any part of our site or other services directed to children under the age of 10. We will close any accounts used exclusively by such children and will remove and/or delete any personal data we believe was submitted by any child under the age of 10. 

### PROTECTION OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal data on our systems. User personal data is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. We will retain personal data in accordance with the Privacy Laws and/or other applicable laws. That is, we will destroy or anonymize your personal data as soon as it is reasonable to assume that (i) the purpose for which that personal data was collected is no longer being served by the retention of such personal data; and (ii) retention is no longer necessary for any legal or business purposes. If you cease using the site, or your permission to use the site and/or the services is terminated, we may continue storing, using and/or disclosing your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our obligations under the Privacy Laws. Subject to applicable law, we may securely dispose of your personal data without prior notice to you. 

### DISCLAIMER

WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA AND/OR OTHER INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE ON THIRD PARTY SITES. We do implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal data that is in our possession or under our control. Your personal data is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the personal data confidential. When you place orders or access your personal data, we offer the use of a secure server. All personal data or sensitive information you supply is encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. 

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may choose various third party websites to link to, and frame within, the site. We may also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies as well as security arrangements. Even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. 

We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content, security arrangements (or lack thereof) and activities of these linked sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and the links placed upon each of them and therefore welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including, without limitation, if a specific link does not work). 

### TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION OVERSEAS

Your personal data and/or information may be transferred to, stored or processed outside of your country. In most cases, your personal data will be processed in Singapore, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. We will only transfer your information overseas in accordance with Privacy Laws. 

### OPT-OUT OR MODIFY INFORMATION

To modify your email subscriptions, please let us know by sending an email to our Personal Data Protection Officer at the address listed below. Please note that due to email production schedules, you may still receive emails that are already in production. 

You may withdraw your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal data in our possession or under our control by sending an email. 

Once we have your clear withdrawal instructions and verified your identity, we will process your request for withdrawal of consent, and will thereafter not collect, use and/or disclose your personal data in the manner stated in your request. If we are unable to verify your identity or understand your instructions, we will liaise with you to understand your request. 

However, your withdrawal of consent could result in certain legal consequences arising from such withdrawal. In this regard, depending on the extent of your withdrawal of consent for us to process your personal data, it may mean that we will not be able to continue providing the services to you, we may need to terminate your existing relationship and/or the contract you have with us, etc., as the case may be, which we will inform you of. 

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices or your dealings with the services, please do not hesitate to contact If you have any complaint or grievance regarding how we are handling your personal data or about how we are complying with Privacy Laws, we welcome you to contact us with your complaint or grievance. 

### PLAYONE ASIA SDN. BHD 

Unit 3A-02, Level 3A, Wisma N2N, Tower 2, Avenue 3, Bangsar South, No. 8, JalanKerinchi, 59200 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia customerservice@playone.asia 

### CHANGES OF PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We advise that you check this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. 

Last Updated: August 25, 2015
